// create a list of questions and answers
var questionList = [
  {
      "question": "1 - Who invented JavaScript?",
      "a": "Douglas Crockford",
      "b": "Sheryl Sandberg",
      "c": "Bill Gates",
      "d": "Brendan Eich",
      "correct": "d",
      "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
      "question": "2 - Which one of these is a JavaScript package manager?",
      "a": "Node.js",
      "b": "TypeScript",
      "c": "npm",
      "d": "jquery",
      "correct": "c",
      "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
      "question": "3 - Which tool can you use to ensure code quality?",
      "a": "Angular",
      "b": "jQuery",
      "c": "RequireJS",
      "d": "ESLint",
      "correct": "d",
      "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
      "question": "4 - Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed in the specified size as if it were in a <font size = 'size'> tag?",
      "a": "fontsize()",
      "b": "fontcolor()",
      "c": "fixed()",
      "d": "bold()",
      "correct": "a",
      "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
      "question": "5 - Which of the following function of String object returns the calling string value converted to lower case?",
      "a": "toLocaleLowerCase()",
      "b": "toLowerCase()",
      "c": "toString()",
      "d": "substring()",
      "correct": "b",
      "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
      "question": "6 - Which of the following function of String object returns the characters in a string between two indexes into the string?",
      "a": "slice()",
      "b": "split()",
      "c": "substr()",
      "d": "substring()",
      "correct": "d",
      "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
      "question": "7 - Which of the following function of Number object returns a string value version of the current number in a format that may vary according to a browser's locale settings.?",
      "a": "toExponential()",
      "b": "toFixed()",
      "c": "toLocaleString()",
      "d": "jtoString()",
      "correct": "c",
      "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
      "question": "8- - Which built-in method calls a function for each element in the array?",
      "a": "while()",
      "b": "loop()",
      "c": "forEach()",
      "d": "None of the above.",
      "correct": "c",
      "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
      "question": "9 - Which of the following function of Array object creates a new array with all of the elements of this array for which the provided filtering function returns true?",
      "a": "concat()",
      "b": "filter()",
      "c": "every()",
      "d": "some()",
      "correct": "b",
      "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
      "question": "10 - Which of the following function of Array object adds and/or removes elements from an array?",
      "a": "splice()",
      "b": "sort()",
      "c": "toSource()",
      "d": "unshift()",
      "correct": "a",
      "userAnswer": null
  },
  
  
];